breakingisraelnews.com 2019-11-01

# Privacy Policy - Breaking Israel News | Latest News. Biblical Perspective.

This Online Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect on our Sites, how we may use the information, with whom we may share it and the choices available to you regarding our use of the information. We also describe the measures we take to safeguard the information and tell you how to contact us about our privacy practices. This privacy policy applies to the Sites and all products and services offered by Israel365.(www.israel365.com, www.breakingisraelnews.com, www.theisraelbible.com, www.yeshivaforthenations.com, www.israelmedianetwork.com)

## **Information We Collect**

We may obtain certain personal information (such as name and other contact details) when you choose to provide them through our Sites by including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, subscribe to a mailing list, respond to a survey, fill out a form, leave a comment, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Sites. You can always refuse to supply personally Identifying information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site related activities. The types of personal information we may collect include:

  * Contact information, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number
  * date of birth
  * username and password
  * personal information in content you provide on our Site (such as text you submit in a chat window on the Site)

In addition, when you visit our Sites, your browser will automatically provide certain information to us. The information we collect in this manner includes anonymized IP address, browser characteristics, device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, information on actions taken on our site, dates and times of website visits, and other technical information.

We may also collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Through these automated collection methods, we obtain “clickstream data,” which is a log of content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website. As the visitor clicks through the website, a record of the action may be collected and stored. If you wish to disable the storage of cookies on your computer, you may do so using the settings on your browser or device. You are also able to [opt out](https://breakingisraelnewscom.kinsta.cloud/cookies/) of storing our cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our Site. For more information on deleting or controlling cookies in general, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/).

If you engage with us via third-party social networking services (such as Facebook), we may receive information you have made available to those services, including the geographic location of your mobile device and other information about you (such as name, email address, gender, locale, time zone, languages, social media profile URL, personal website URL, biographical information, birthday, photo, list of devices, education history, work history, hometown, interests, current city, political views, favorite athlete and teams, relationship status and information, religion, name of significant other, and certain security settings information) and your contacts on those services. You should make sure you understand the information your third-party social networking services may make available to our Site. We may use and disclose the personal information we receive through third-party social networking services as described in this Online Privacy Policy.

## **How We Use The Information We Collect**

We may use the information we obtain through the Site to:

  * create and manage your account;
  * conduct the transaction you request;
  * offer and provide products and services to you;
  * communicate with you about our products and services (including via social media);
  * administer your participation in special events, programs, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and other offers or promotions (if you have not opted out of receiving such information _)_ ;
  * display content on our Sites, such as stories, product reviews and photos;
  * respond to and communicate with you about your requests, questions and comments;
  * process claims we receive in connection with our products and services;
  * operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; determining the effectiveness of our sales, marketing and advertising; analyzing and enhancing our products, services and Sites; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities);
  * perform data analyses and other processing (including market and consumer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, anonymization, encryption or tokenization of personal information);
  * protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities; and
  * comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies.

In addition, we use information collected online through cookies, web beacons and other automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users’ visits to our Sites, (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users’ interests and the manner in which our users browse our Sites, and (iii) managing our business. We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, administer our Sites, identify users of our Sites, and gather demographic information about our users. We use clickstream data to determine how much time users spend on web pages of our Sites, how users navigate through our Sites, and how we may tailor our Sites to better meet the needs of our users.

We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Sites.

Sensitive and private data exchange between our Sites and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

## **Online Tracking**

We may use third-party web analytics services on our Site, such as those of Google Analytics. The analytics providers that administer these services use technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons to help us analyze how visitors use our Sites. The information collected through these means (including IP address) is disclosed to these analytics providers, who use the information to evaluate use of our Sites. To learn more about Google Analytics and how to opt out, please visit [www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245).

Our Sites are not designed to respond to “do not track” signals received from browsers.

On our Sites, we may collect information about your online activities for use in providing you with advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests.

You may see certain ads on other websites based on your visits to our Sites because we participate in advertising networks administered by third-party vendors. Ad networks allow us to target our messaging to users considering demographic data, users’ inferred interests and browsing context. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs and web beacons. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that are tailored to your individual interests. The information our ad network vendors collect includes information about your visits to websites that participate in the vendors’ advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the websites. This data collection takes place both on our Sites and on third-party websites that participate in the ad networks. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. To learn more about how to opt out of ad network interest-based advertising, [click here](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

## **Information We Share**

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others, except as described in this Online Privacy Policy. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personally identifying information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.When you post a product review on our Site, we may publish your name on the Site with your review or repost your name and review on other websites. We share the personal information we obtain with third parties who perform services on our behalf. These third parties may include mail houses and payment processors that process and fulfill your orders. These third parties are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. We also may share the personal information we obtain with marketing affiliates and service providers who help us market our products to consumers and drive traffic to our Site or provide other marketing or related services. In addition, we may share personal information with our corporate affiliates, who may use the information on our behalf or for their own purposes.

We also may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena), (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities, (iii) for the purpose of or in connection with legal proceedings, or otherwise for the purpose of establishing, exercising or defending our legal rights, or (iv) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).

**WHAT RIGHTS YOU HAVE OVER YOUR DATA**

Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to (i) access certain personal information we maintain about you and obtain a copy of that information, (ii) update or correct inaccuracies in that information, (iii) object to our use of your personal information where it is likely to cause damage or distress and (iv) delete your personal information from our database. To exercise these rights, please contact us as indicated in the How To Contact Us section of this Online Privacy Notice. To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we may take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the information. Subject to applicable law, a charge may apply before we provide a copy to you of any of your personal information that we maintain. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## **Links To Other Websites**

Our Site may contain links to other websites for your convenience and information such as, partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties These websites may be operated by companies not affiliated with us.  These websites may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of any websites that are not affiliated with us, any use of those websites, or the privacy practices of those websites.

## **Direct Marketing**

From time to time we may send information to you regarding products and services, promotions and other information that may be of interest to you, using the contact details that you provide to us.

We have various email lists that you may have opted in to, through our different sites. You may fully unsubscribe from any of our email lists at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every email. You may also reply to the email asking to unsubscribe or by contacting us at the address listed in the How To Contact Us section.

It is possible to opt out of promotional emails while continuing to receive our daily emails. This can be done by clicking the “Update Profile” or “Subscription Preferences” link found in the bottom of every email or by replying to the email or by contacting us at the address listed in the How to Contact Us section.

Unsubscribing from one list does not unsubscribe you from all lists. After you unsubscribe from a list,  we will not send you further emails from that list. We may continue, however, to email you as reasonably necessary in connection with the administration of your account.

## **Data Transfers**

For the purpose of operating our business, including to fulfill orders you place with us, we may transfer the personal information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected in accordance with the provisions of this Online Privacy Notice. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Online Privacy Notice and in accordance with applicable law.

This may include transferring your personal information to jurisdictions outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), including the United States. We may use facilities in countries outside the EEA to carry out specific operations involving your personal information (e.g., IT and hosting services). Where your personal information is collected in the EEA and we then transfer it outside the EEA, we will strive to ensure that an adequate level of protection is in place to protect your personal information.

## **Your Options**

We offer you certain choices about how we communicate with you and what information we collect from you. To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists or submit a request, please contact us as specified in the How To Contact Us section of this Online Privacy Policy.

## **How We Protect Personal Information**

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Online Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices.When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using our Sites, services and subscribing to our emails. you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Sites, services or subscribe to our emails. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions about this Online Privacy Policy, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please [contact us.](https://breakingisraelnewscom.kinsta.cloud/contact-us/)

_This document was last updated on May, 28, 2018._
